Okay. Are you from
the Star Wars universe?
好吧 你是来自吗
Yes.
是的
- Were you in the original trilogy?
- Yes.
- 你是原三部曲里的吗?
- 是的
Oh,is tre a picture of you in
my llet wearing metal bikini?
噢 我钱包里照片上那个
穿着金属比基尼的是你吗
God,I hope not.
老天 我希望不是
And no,I'm not Princess Leia.
不是 我不是莉亚公主
Okay,okay. My turn.
好了 好了 该我了
- Are you in all six Star Wars movies?
- Yes.
- 你在六部都出现过吗?
- 是的
- Interestg. Are you a droid?
- Yes.
- 有趣 你是机器人吗?
- 是的
Do you kind of look
like a shiny Sheldon?
你长的像闪闪发光的Sheldon吗?
Yes.
没错
- C-3PO. -
You got it.
- C-3PO
- 猜对了!
That's preposterous. I
do not resemble C-3PO.
这太荒谬了 我和C-3PO没有任何相似之处
Don't get me wrong. I'm
flattered. I just don't see it.
别误会 事实上我受宠若惊
我没看出来罢了
Leslie Winkle.
Leslie Winkle
You've reached "Friends with Benefits."
你接通了"非常朋友"热线
For a booty call,press one now.
想找"炮友" 请按1号键
What exactly does that expression
mean,friends with benefits?
"非常朋友"到底非常在哪里了?
Does he provide her
with health insurance?
他为她提供健康保险了?
No. Look,uh...
不 是这样 呃...
Imagine you maintained a friendship
with someone you had sex with,
想像一下你和性伴侣维持朋友关系
but you were free to
date whoever you wanted.
同时你又可以自由和任何人约会
I'm sorry. I can't imagine any of that.
抱歉 我完全想象不出
All right. Back to the game.
我看咱们还是接着游戏吧
I believe it's my turn.
应该轮到我了
You may begin your questions
whenever you're ready.
你们准备好了就可以开始提问
Are you Spock?
你是史波克吗?
I don't like this game.
我不喜欢这游戏
So,where were we?
我们刚才说到哪儿了?
Aren't you leaving for your booty call?
你不去赴"炮友"之约吗?
No,it was something else.
不 是别的事
Why does everything have to
be about sex with you? Come on.
为什么所有事情都要跟性扯上关系? 拜托~
- Whose turn is it?
- We were up to you.
- 轮到谁了?
- 到你了 我们正等着呢
Great. Just start.
很好 开始吧
Okay,let's see. Are
you from a TV series?
好 你是电视剧里的人物吗
She dumped me!
她把我甩了!
I bet he's someone from Babylon
5. We're never going to get it.
我打赌他一定是里的
我们永远也猜不着
荣誉出品
翻译: 冰啤梨果橙 饭特稀 樱桃小超人
校对: penny
时间轴: 咔肉肉
What happened with Leslie?
Why did she dump you?
Leslie怎么了? 她为什么要甩你?
I don't know. She just
said,Howard,Mama's a rolling stone.
我不知道 她只是说
Howard 妈妈是见异思迁的人
Then her call waiting
beeped and she was gone.
然后她的电话就变成语音留言
她离开了我
I don't understand.
我不太明白
If you were in a
non-emotional relationship,
既然这是不谈情只谈性的关系
then why are you having what
appears to be an emotional response?
你为什么会对分手有如此情绪化的反应?
Sheldon,he obviously
had feelings for her.
Sheldon 他显然是对她有感情了
Of course I had feelings for her.
我当然对她有感情
I saw her naked,for God's sake.
我看见她赤果果了 拜托
Okay,look,you just need
to get your mind off it.
好吧 瞧 你现在需要彻底忘记这些
Do you want to go to
the comic book store?
你想去漫画书店吗?
Maybe go see a movie?
或者去看电影?
I don't want to go anywhere.
我哪儿也不想去
You know,I'm given to understand
that there's an entire city in Nevada
根据我的印象 在内华达州有一个城市
designed specifically to help people
like Howard forget their problems.
是专为Howard这种想要
忘记烦心事儿的人设计的
They can replace them with new
problems such as alcoholism,
他们能让新问题取代老问题 比如酗酒
gambling addiction,and
sexually transmitted diseases.
嗜赌成性还有性传播疾病等
Is it me,or was that Sheldon's
way of saying,"Vegas,baby!"?
是我理解错了 还是Sheldon在说
"拉斯维加斯 宝贝儿!"?
I've never been there. Have you?
我从没去过那里 你去过吗?
Me? No. I just got "Vegas,baby!"
from Vince Vaughn in Swingers.
我? 没 这句"拉斯维加斯 宝贝儿!"
不过是跟里文斯・沃恩学的
It could be fun. I know my
weekend's wide open,now that...
蛮有意思的样子 我周末闲着呢 现在又...
Okay,let's do this.
Let's go to Las Vegas.
好吧 决定了 我们去拉斯维加斯
Now? Right now?
现在? 说走就走?
Why not? People do things
"right now," all the time.
为什么不? 人们总是会说干啥就干啥
Why can't we be "right now" people,too?
为啥咱不能"说走就走"呢?
Go home,pack a bag,and
we'll be "right now" people.
去 收拾行李 咱也潮一把 说走就走
I mean,I have to stop at the drug
store to refill a prescription,
我是说 我得先去药店再抓点药
but after that,we'll go right now.
但那之后 我们说走就走
What do you say,Howard?
你怎么说 Howard
I say... Vegas,baby!
我想说...拉斯维加斯 宝贝儿!
What are you going to tell your mother?
那你怎么跟你老妈交待?
Sea World,baby!
海洋世界 宝贝儿!
y,Sheldon,are you coming?
嘿 Sheldon 你去吗?
I'd rather have a blowfly lay eggs
and hatch larvae in my auditory canal.
我宁愿让苍蝇在我耳朵里产卵然后孵化
Great. We'll bring you back a t-shirt.
好吧 我们会给你带一件T恤回来
Thank you.
谢谢
- Hello,neighbor.
- Hello,Sheldon.
- 你好 邻居
- 你好 Sheldon
And how are you this fine evening?
这个美好的晚上你过得如何?
- Great.
- Good. I'm glad.
- 很好
- 好 我很高兴
Really? Are you drunk?
真的吗? 你喝醉了吧?
I'm just in a good mood.
我这是心情好呀
While my compatriots are in Las Vegas,
我的伙伴们去了拉斯维加斯
I will be enjoying a blissful evening
in my personal Fortress of Solitude.
我可以在我专属的孤独城堡里
度过一个愉悦的夜晚
That's Superman's big ice thingy,right?
就是超人那个大冰窖 对吧?
You know,I'm in such a good mood,
你知道吗 我心情如此之好
I'm actually finding your tenuous grasp of
the English language folksy and charming today.
以至于觉得你英语的薄弱理解力
在我看来都变得亲切和迷人了
What smells so good?
什么东西闻起来这么香?
That is the intoxicating
aroma of Kadhai Paneer,
那是印度奶酪散发出的醉人芳香
a perfect culinary representation
of the freedom this evening holds.
它正象征着这个美好的自由之夜
Not only is it Indian
cuisine,which Koothrappali loathes,
它不仅是Koothrappali讨厌的印度食品
it contains a generous
helping of peanuts,
里面还有大份的花生
which would reduce Wolowitz
to a wheezing 97-pound blister.
足以让Wolowitz变成个
97磅的直喘气的大水疱
And finally,its main
ingredient is paneer,
最后 它的主料是凝乳干酪
a farmer's cheese that would cause Leonard to
render any room uninhabitable within minutes.
这种普通的农夫干酪
能让Leonard跟哪儿呆着都坐立不安
Yum.
很美味哦
Well,enjoy your big evening.
好吧 好好享受你这个盛大的夜晚
Penny. I realize you're also on
your own tonight,so if,at some point,
Penny 我发现你今晚也是一个人
所以如果 在某个时候
you find yourself with nothing
to do,please do not disturb me.
你感觉到无聊了 请千万不要来打扰我
Have fun,Sheldon.
玩的愉快 Sheldon
Oh,I shall.
噢 我会的
No!
不~!
What's wrong,Superman? Locked
out of your big ice thingy?
怎么了 超人? 被你的大冰窖拒之门外了?
Look at this.
Mouthwash,lotion,body wash.
瞧瞧这些 漱口水 乳液 沐浴露
Shampoo and conditioner
together in one tiny bottle.
洗发水和护发素浓缩在一小瓶子里
I love Las Vegas.
我爱拉斯维加斯
Howard,could I borrow some aftershave?
Howard 能借用一下须后水吗?
Black case,top compartment.
黑色包包 上面那层
That's a lot of cologne.
古龙水也太多了吧
First row are your musks.
第一排是麝香味的
Second is woods,leathers and botanicals.
第二排是木香 皮革香和植物香系列
Third is assorted
pheromones. Tread lightly.
第三排是各种外激素 别乱用哟
That's the spirit,Howard.
Howard 这才是美国精神
Yes,we can.
我们能行
Come on. Let's go.
快 走吧
You guys go ahead. I just
have to finish up an email.
你们俩先去吧 我得写完这封Email
That's not an email. That's
Leslie's Facebook page.
这哪是Email 是Leslie的Facebook页面
Okay,fine. I'm checking
her Facebook page.
好吧 我在看她的Facebook页面
Look at her status update.
She's saying she dumped me.
瞧瞧她的最新动态
她说她甩了我
People need to know I dumped her.
别人应该知道是我甩了她
But she did dump you.
可确实是她甩了你
Grow up,Raj. There's no place
for truth on the Internet.
别天真了 Raj
真相在因特网上是无处容身的
Just go. I'll catch up with you.
你们先走 我等会儿就来
All right.
行
Oh,we should have a plan in
case one of us gets lucky.
噢 我们得制定个计划
以防万一我们中有谁走桃花运
Okay,uh,if I get lucky,I'll take her to my
stately manner outside Gotham City,and...
好啊 如果我走运的话
我会带她去哥谭市外的豪宅
if you get lucky,I'll sleep on the moon.
而要是你走运了 我就睡月亮上
Sounds like a plan.
听着不赖
Hang on. I think the emergency
key is around here somewhere.
等下 我觉得备用钥匙就在这附近
We have a bowl.
我们有个碗
Our keys go in a bowl.
我们把钥匙放在那个碗里
You should get a bowl.
你也该弄个碗
So,how did the beautiful mind of Sheldon
Cooper forget his key in the first place?
那么 Sheldon Cooper的完美大脑
怎么会忘带钥匙了呢?
I left them in the bowl.
我把它放在碗里了
- I just remembered where the emergency key is.
- Where?
- 我记得备用钥匙在哪儿
- 哪儿?
In your apartment.
你屋里
What's it doing in my apartment?
怎么跑到我们那去了?
Well,I went in there a few weeks ago and
you guys weren't home and I forgot it there.
我几个礼拜前去你们那儿
你们正巧不在 我就忘在那儿了
You went in my... Why
would... What are you saying?
你去了我的... 为什么...
你在说什么?
It's not a big deal. I was making
coffee and I ran out of milk.
又没啥大不了的
我不过是泡咖啡时没牛奶了
You're the milk thief!
你是那个偷奶贼!
Leonard said I was crazy,but I
knew that carton felt lighter.
Leonard说我多心了
可我就是觉得盒子变轻了
All right. Sheldon,look. Just calm down.
好吧 Sheldon 冷静一点
I will call the building manager
and he'll come open your door.
我给大楼管理员打电话
他会来替你开门的
You just eat your dinner
here while you're waiting.
反正要在这儿等着
不如就把晚饭吃了吧
Eat? My dinner? In your apartment?
在你屋里? 吃? 晚饭?
Yeah. Why not?
是啊 有何不可?
Sure. Why not?
没错 有何不可?
And after the sun's down,we can all pile in my
pickup and go skinny-dipping down at the crick.
在日落之后 可以挤进我的皮卡
一起去裸泳 游到它抽筋为止
'Cause today's the day
to stop making sense.
今天开始 一切都蛮不讲理了
Thanks.
谢了
I'm telling you,Leonard...
video slots...
我跟你说 Leonard 游戏屏...
free drinks brought to us by a bosomy
barmaid and all you can eat shrimp for $3.95.
丰满的酒吧女递来的免费饮料
还有3.95美元畅吃的大虾
Disneyland can suck it.
迪斯尼乐园该关门了
This is the real
happiest place on earth.
这才是世上最快乐的地方
Dude,check it out!
老兄 瞧瞧!
That's laundry for a month!
一个月的洗衣服务!
Hello.
你好
- What's your name?
- Rajesh Ramayan Koothrappali.
- 尊姓大名?
- Rajesh Ramayan Koothrappali
Hello,Rajesh
Ra-- Hi,Rajesh.
你好 Rajesh Ra... 嗨 Rajesh
I'm Michaela.
我叫Michaela
Hello,Michaela.
你好 Michaela
So,you interested in a little party?
去狂欢你有兴趣吗?
Why,yes,I love to party.
当然 我喜欢狂欢
Party is my middle name.
狂欢是我的中间名
Or,it would be if it weren't Ramayan.
或者说 如果不是Ramayan的话就是了
Uh,Raj,can I... can I
talk to you for a moment?
呃 Raj 能不能...
能不能借一步说话?
Not now,Leonard. Michaela's
inviting me to a party.
现在不行 Leonard
Michaela邀请我去狂欢呢
You better call the moon and
make sure they have a bed for you.
你最好打电话上月球
问问那儿还有没有你的床位
Yeah. I really need to talk to you.
我真的要和你谈谈
Excuse me. I'll be right back.
Don't go anywhere. Don't move.
抱歉 我马上就回来
别走噢 也别动
Just stay the beautiful,unspoiled
American flower that you are.
保持你那种美式的含苞待放之美
What's wrong with you,dude? That
woman was all up in my jammy.
老兄 你是怎么了?
那个女人已经和我勾搭上了
Okay.I hate to break this to
you and whatever your "jammy" is,
好 我也不想给你晴天霹雳
坏了你的"勾搭"好事
but I'm pretty sure she's a prostitute.
但我十分肯定她是个妓女
What? No...
什么? 不...
Let me put it this way:
In your entire life,
这么说吧 在你这辈子中
how many gorgeous women have walked straight up
to you in a bar and asked if you wanted to party?
有多少漂亮女人会在酒吧里
径直走向你 问你要不要出去狂欢?
Maybe I can save her.
也许我能拯救她
Maybe,but I'm guessing it'll cost
you about $500 an hour to try.
也许吧 但估计你试那一下
一个小时得花你500美刀
It was lovely meeting you.
很高兴认识你
Best of luck in your future endeavors.
祝你今后好运
Whatever.
随便
Oh,I miss her already.
噢 我已经开始想她了
Oh,Howard's losing it.
哦 Howard崩了
Check out his latest Twitters.
看看他最新的Twitter
"I'm at the bottom of a black
holE staring into the abyss."
"我身处黑洞的底部望向无尽深渊"
My life is meaningless.
My future is without hope."
"我的人生毫无意义
我的未来尽失希望"
Why don't we take him to
see the Blue Man Group?
带他去看蓝人乐团如何?
(三个戴蓝头套穿黑衣服的音乐人)
You think that'd help?
你觉得这有用?
USA Today calls them "exuberant
fun for the whole family."
今日美国把他们称作
"全家人的非凡乐趣"
I don't know. Howard isn't
really the family fun kind of guy.
我不清楚 Howard不像是那种
对家庭娱乐感兴趣的人
It's too bad he wasn't
here for that hooker.
可惜了 他没能遇上那妓女
She's exactly his type; a hooker.
她完全贴合他的要求 一个妓女
You know,I bet if we hired
her,that would cheer him up.
我打赌 如果我们雇了她
她能让他打起精神来的
We're not gonna get Wolowitz a hooker.
我们不能给Wolowitz召妓
"I'm so lonely and horny,I may open
this $20 jar of peanuts and end it all."
"我是如此孤独而又饥渴
也许该干掉这罐20块的花生 结束一切"
I suppose it wouldn't
hurt to get an estimate.
我想评估一下应该不会有问题
So how was your day?
你今天如何呀?
Are you trying to make small talk?
你想跟我聊聊?
Oh,sweetie,you really don't have to.
噢 亲爱的 真的没这必要
No,it's the accepted convention.
不 这叫约定俗成
How was your day?
你今天如何呀?
Well,uh,they shifted my schedule around at the
restaurant,so my hours are gonna be a little differe...
餐厅的人调整了我的时间表
所以我上班的时间会有一点儿不同...
I'm sorry. That's not going to
interest me at all. Just eat.
抱歉 我对此完全不感兴趣 吃就是了
Hello again.
又是我
Yeah,hi. Listen,um...
你好 听着 嗯...
if you're not busy,we were
thinking maybe you could...
要是你不忙的话
我们在想你是不是可以...
We were wondering...
我们在想...
if you're really a prostitute.
你是不是真的是妓女
- You guys cops?
- No.
- 你们是警察?
- 不
I'm a prostitute.
我是妓女
Okay,great.
太棒了
Uh,the thing is,we've got this
friend,and he's kind of down in the dumps.
事情是这样的 我们有个朋友
他最近有点儿情绪低落
And we thought maybe
you could cheer him up.
我们觉着也许你能让他打起精神来
With sex.
OOXX
I think she knows what I meant.
我觉得她明白我的意思
How can she when you beat around the bh?
你拐弯抹角的她怎么能明白?
She's from the mean streets where they
shoot from the hip and keep it real.
她们那边都是直来直去的
Don't worry. I can take
good care of your friend.
别担心 我可以照料好你们的朋友
Okay,terrific.
太好了
listen,is there a way that we can do
this where he doesn't know that you're a,
你有没有办法可以
让他察觉不出来你...
- you know...
- Prostitute.
- 你知道的
- 是个妓女
You want the girlfriend experience.
想要女友般的体验?
Yes. Yeah,exactly. The
girlfriend experience.
对 没错 就是女友般的体验
Actually,if it's not too much to ask,could
we have the Jewish girlfriend experience?
实际上 不知道算不算过分
能来犹太女友的体验吗?
Okay,that's question
20. You have to guess.
好 这是第20问了 你得猜猜看
I don't know,Sheldon. Are you Star Wars?
我不知道 Sheldon
你扮演的是星际大战?
How can one person be a whole movie?
一个人如何能够扮演一整部电影
Okay,I give up. Can we
just do something else?
算了 我放弃 我们能干点别的吗
Fine.
那好
I was Spock.
我是史波克
Are you and Leonard
friends with benefits?
你和Leonard是"非常朋友"吗?
What?
什么?
Are you and Leonard
friends with benefits?
你和Leonard是"非常朋友"吗
Where did that even come
from? Did he say we were?
何来此话 是他这么说的吗
No,Leonard said nothing.
不 Leonard什么也没说
But who knows what goes on over here when
he pretends your mail was misdelivered?
可他假装你的信送错了地方
谁知道你们俩到底怎么回事
Just mail,no benefits.
只是送信 没非常关系
I see.
明白了
Why are you asking?
干嘛问这个
I'm curious about the
whole social construct.
我对整个社交构成结构感到好奇
On its face,the idea of
satisfying one's sexual appetite--
从表面来看 满足一个人的性欲...
assuming one is
afflicted with such--
假如说有人遭受此事
without emotional entanglement,that
seems eminently practical.
又没有感情纠葛 是非常现实的关系
What I've observed,however,is Howard
Wolowitz crying like a little girl.
然而现在是 Howard Wolowitz
哭哭啼啼的 就像个小女孩
Well,some people just can't
handle that kind of relationship.
有些人就是没办法处理好这种感情
Can you?
那你行吗
Excuse me?
什么意思
Are you able to have sex with men without
developing an emotional attachment?
你可以与男人发生关系
同时不掺杂任何感情进去吗
Sheldon,I really don't want
to talk about this with you.
Sheldon 我真不想和你讨论这个
Is this conversation
making you uncomfortable?
这谈话让你感到不自在了吗
Of course it's making me
uncomfortable. Can't you tell?
当然让我不自在 你看不出来吗
I really have no idea.I don't particularly
excel at reading facial expressions,
我不清楚 我不擅长阅读面部表情
- body language...
- I'm uncomfortable,Sheldon!
- 肢体语言...
- 我很不自在 Sheldon!
Thank you. That's very helpful.
谢谢 我懂了
All right,where are
these amazing shrimp?
好吧 美味小虾在哪
Behold.
看这里
Seriously,you think this
is the size of a baby's arm?
说真的 你说和婴儿胳膊一般大小
就是这样子的?
A little baby.
小小婴儿
Okay,I'm going back to the room.
好 我还是回家吧
Boy,would it maybe kill them
to put out a nice brisket?
让他们上一盘上等胸肉就这么困难
Hi,there. Howard Wolowitz.
你好 我是Howard Wolowitz
Esther Rosenblatt.
Esther Rosenblatt
I don't think the manager's
coming tonight,so here.
我觉得管理员今晚是不会来了 给你
Are you suggesting I sleep on the couch?
你是准备让我睡沙发吗
Well,it wasn't the first suggestion that
came to mind,but it's the one I'm going with.
虽然不是我的最初想法
不过我现在是这么打算的
I can't sleep on your
couch. I sleep in a bed.
我没法睡你的沙发
我都是在床上睡觉的
And given its dimensions,
瞧瞧这尺寸
I have no intention of living out
E.M.Snickering's beloved children's book,
我可不想像E.M.Snickering的
流行儿童读物中那个
The Tall Man From Cornwall.
康沃尔的大个子一样睡觉
What?
那是什么
"There was a tall man from Cornwall
whose length exceeded his bed."
从前在康沃尔有个大个子
他的身高要长过自己的床
"My body fits on it,but barely upon
it,there's no room for my big Cornish head."
这张床我的身子躺着刚刚好
可我的头却没有地方放
All right,I will give you
my bed on one condition:
好吧 我让出床 不过有一个条件
that you promise to zip your
hole for the next eight hours.
未来8小时内把你那窟窿闭好
- May I say one last thing?
- Only if it doesn't rhyme.
- 我还能再说一句吗
- 不押韵就行
All right.
那好吧
Good night.
晚安啦
Turn-ons? Let me see.
感性趣的事 让我想想
Reading a good book in front of
the fire,long walks on the beach...
在壁炉前读本好书 在沙滩上漫步
and getting freaky on the
Sabbath with a bacon cheeseburger.
在安息日里放纵一下 吃培根芝士汉堡
Really? Me,too!
是吗 我也是哎
Oy,gevalt,you're hot.
噢 天呐 你真性感
Yeah.
是吗
Excuse me for a moment.
稍等一下
- Hey,how's it going?
- Cut the crap. You set this up,didn't you?
- 进展如何
- 少废话 你们安排的 对不对
Yes. She'a hooker,**
- 对
- 她是只鸡 对吧
A prostitute,yes.
是妓女 没错
- You already gave her the money?
- Yes.
- 你们已经付了钱
- 对
Thank you!
太感谢啦
Penny?
What?
干嘛
I can't sleep.
我睡不着
Maybe that's because
your hole is still open.
也许是因为你的大窟窿还张着
I'm homesick.
我想家
Your home is 20 feet from here.
你家离这不过20尺
20 feet,20 light-years,it
doesn't matter.
20尺还是20光年这都不重要
It's in a galaxy far,far away.
在我这 如同一个星系那么遥远
Damn it.
可恶
What do you want me to do?
你想让我怎么办
Sing "Soft Kitty."
给我唱"软软凯蒂猫"
That's only for when you're sick.
那是只有你生病时才唱的歌
Homesick is a type of being sick.
思家也是一种病
Come on,do I really have to?
拜托 真的要唱吗
I suppose we can stay up and talk.
那设想下我们通宵达旦 闲话家常
* Soft kitty,warm kitty
* 软软凯蒂 柔柔凯蒂 *
* Little ball of fur
* 一团小毛球 *
* Happy kitty...
* 快乐凯蒂... *
Sleepy kitty.
睡睡凯蒂
- * Sleepy kit...
- No.
- * 睡睡凯... *
- 不对
Start over.
重来
* Soft kitty,warm kitty
* 软软凯蒂 柔柔凯蒂 *
* Little ball of fur
* 一团小毛球 *
* Happy kitty,sleepy kitty
* 快乐凯蒂 睡睡凯蒂 *
* Purr,purr,purr.
* 喵 喵 喵 *
- Penny?
- Yeah?
- 嗯
Thank you for letting me stay here.
谢谢你留我在这过夜
You're welcome,sweetie.
不客气 甜心
Okay,I'm sleepy now. Get out.
好 我已经困了 你出去
Oh,good. You're finally home.
太好了 你总算回来了
What were you doing at Penny's?
你在Penny家干什么
Well,we had dinner,uh,played some
games,and then I spent the night.
我们一起吃了晚饭 做游戏
之后我在那过的夜
You'll be happy to know that I now have a much
better understanding of "friends with benefits."
哦 告诉你一件好事哦
我对"非常朋友"有了更深入的了解